bowvalleycollege.ca 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy

**Commitment**

Bow Valley College is committed to providing our visitors with a website that respects their privacy. This page summarizes the privacy policy and practices on the Bow Valley College website.

**Links to Other Websites**  
This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content and the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read the privacy policy of each site that you visit before proceeding further.

**Cookies**  
Some websites store information in a small text file, called a "cookie," on your hard disk. Cookies contain information about you and your preferences (e.g., a record of which pages within the site you visited) to help the site customize the view for you the next time you visit. Only the information that you provide, or the choices you make while visiting a website, can be stored in a cookie. For example, the site cannot determine your e-mail name unless you choose to provide it.

Allowing a website to create a cookie does not give that or any other site access to the rest of your computer, and only the site that created the cookie can read it.

Cookies can be enabled/disabled by selecting Tools -> Internet Options. Select the Security tab and then select Custom Level. The cookie settings will be displayed in the Security Settings dialog box.

This website does not use cookies or any other means of collecting information about you or your computer without your knowledge.

**Personal Information Collected Through This Website**

We do not automatically gather any personal information from you, such as your name, phone number, e-mail, or address. If you send us e-mail or use our feedback form to contact us, you will be providing us with some personal information including your name, e-mail and perhaps information about your personal circumstances. This information is only used to process and respond to your question or comment, and is collected in compliance with the Alberta Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (the FOIP Act). This information is not disclosed except to authorized personnel who need it to answer your question.

Bow Valley College is subject to the Alberta government's [Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act](http://www.servicealberta.ca/foip/).
